UAE Dubai Mobile: +971564552368

Career objective

Seeking a challenging career within a progressive organization where my skills with my vast experiences will enable me to make significant contribution to grow the business in a solid foundation .

Profile

A highly skillful well experienced senior manager has more than 15 years experiences in sales, marketing, operation, supply chain field in various countries. Speak Arabic, English, French fluently and some Italian language. With excellent communication skill, excellent skill on developing new channel, new business and build solid business partnership in Middle East, Africa regions.

Personal Profile

Name : Lynda Boumedine

Gender : Female
Date of Birth : Algiers 1967
Nationality : Algerian
Martial Status : Single

Visa Status : Employment Visa Driving License : UAE driving license

Languages : Arabic (mother tongue), English (fluent), French

(Fluent), Italian (Basic)

Computer Skills : MS Office, Excel

Work Experience

July 2008 till Sep 2016 (9 years) Senior Marketing

Manager / Relationship Manager / Project Manager Roles

Employer: OFFSHORE ENGINEERING & MARKETING - Jebel Ali Free Zone Dubai , UAE

OFFSHORE ENGINEERING & MARKETING LIMITED was established in 1994 as a very well respectful and reliable supplier and an outstanding service provider to its world-wide clients base. Pipe, Fittings, Flanges, Bolts and Gasket Suppliers Based in Dubai & Egypt and Algeria, etc.

Job Responsibilities and Achievements:

- Responsible for the Business Plan, Action Plan, Risk Assessment and Tenders Analysis, project management, team management.
- Registration & qualifying OEML with the clients in the key segment areas.
- Assist Group CEO on International business expansions strategic planning and implementation.



- Assist Group CEO on business management and business development.
- Handling operation, supply chain, sales and marketing activities.
- Leading and Managing the projects: big perspective EPC foreign oil companies projects.
- Develop business in Middle East, Africa regions.

2005 to 2007 (2 years) IFFCO Company - DUBAI, UAE Senior Marketing Executive and Relationship Manager Role

- Prepare the marketing planning and implement the plan.
- · Organize the events in Middle East .
- Compiling and distributing financial and statistical information
- Represent the company to attend the exhibitions and marketing activities.
- Promote company and establish great relationship with clients .

2004 to 2006 (3 years) Gide loyrette & Nouel Company - Algeria Assistant to company owner and Marketing Manager Role

- Produce information by transcribing, formatting, inputting, editing, retrieving, copying, and transmitting text, data, and graphics.
- Handle department personnel; arranging meetings, conferences, teleconferences, and travel activity.
- Prepares reports by collecting information within all departments.
- Handle supply chain management. To evaluate the needed suppliers and communication with suppliers.
- Provides historical reference by utilizing filing and retrieval systems.
- Assist company owner on internal and external communications of company business activities.
- Handle marketing brochures, marketing activities and prepare exhibitions.

Academic Background

- Geophysics Engineer from University of Technology, Algiers, Algeria 1994.
- Training at Sonatrach Company (Oil Company)

Personal Traits

I am an enthusiastic, hardworking, adaptable, and result – oriented professional.